copperbridgemedia.com 2014-11-08

# Privacy Policy | CopperBridge Media

This mandates that we adhere to the highest levels of professionalism and transactional standards which protects our user’s rights and privacy. Please spare a few moments to understand our information collection & dissemination practices.

**PS:** There might be periodic changes in our policies and any such change will be immediately reflected here.

**[a] Personal Information Collection**  
Normal activities like browsing can be performed with the registration process (without sharing any information with CopperBridge Media). But, for account set-up and updates, there is a need for registration – when you share your personal information like Name, Email Address, Phone number etc. This information is used to facilitate a faster check-out and periodic dispatch of offers and news relevant to your purchase pattern.

**[b] Utilization of Demographic information**  
We utilize the demographic information majorly for these objectives…

  * To deliver the services that was requested by you
  * To resolve any conflicts or any outstanding transactions or issues
  * To inform you about any online / offline offers that is aligned with your taste
  * To make your experience better on CopperBridge Media.com
  * Protect you against any online fraud
  * Your IP address might be used to detect any server related issue and to administer our website more efficiently
  * There might be optional surveys intended to improve the level of experience on CopperBridge Media.com
  * This information can also be used to send Newsletters to you – and you can unsubscribe at any point of time

**[c] Sharing of Personal information**  
Any personal information that is collected through our website is transparently utilized for the following reasons…

  * The personal information might be shared with our corporate affiliates or partners to help identify and detect identity theft
  * Prevent misuse of our website by utilizing personal information for correlating related or multiple accounts
  * To facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. These corporate entities will not indulge in marketing unless you explicitly opt-in.
  * Personal information collected through our website will be only disclosed if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.
  * Any personal information collected through our website will be only disclosed to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary. The reasons for disclosure might be linked to – Enforcing the Terms & Policies; Respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

**[d] Sites linked to CopperBridge Media.com**  
CopperBridge Media might have links of sites that collect specific personal information from you. CopperBridge Media.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

**[e] CopperBridge Media security architecture**  
The best security architecture has been utilized on the CopperBridge Media.com site in order to safeguard the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Secure server ensures that any access, addition or modification of account information is achieved in a completely secured environment. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

**[f] At-will opt-out**  
CopperBridge Media.com provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

**[g] Questions?**  
If you have any queries / concerns / recommendations, please utilize the following address:

info@copperbridgemedia.com

Terms & Conditions  
The ‘Terms & Conditions’ contained herein define the guidelines with respect to the usage of copperbridgemedia.com. Kindly browse this document carefully so that you are aware of the general terms and conditions regarding copperbridgemedia.com. There might be periodic updates to this document. It is the discretion of CopperBridge Media to amend the clauses of this document based on the circumstances. Your use of the website after any amendment to the Terms of Use shall constitute your acceptance of these terms and you also agree to be bound by any such changes/revisions. Any clause of ‘Terms & Conditions’ if deemed invalid, void or for any reason unenforceable, shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining clauses of the terms and conditions.

**Terms Glossary:**  

  * “Agreement” means the Terms and Conditions (T&C) contained herein under the copperbridgemedia.com. It will also include references to this agreement as and when amended, notated, supplemented, varied or replaced.
  * “Website” refers to “copperbridgemedia.com” owned and operated by CopperBridge Media, which provides a venue to the users of copperbridgemedia.com to buy the products listed / displayed at copperbridgemedia.com.
  * “Users/User/You” means and includes any Users / Buyer / You (the person or any legal entity) who accept the offer for services by copperbridgemedia.com.

**Terms & Conditions:**  
_This agreement between the users and copperbridgemedia.com is subject to the following terms and conditions:_  

  * The consumer / user certifies that he/she is at least 18 (eighteen) years of age or has the consent of a parent or legal guardian.
  * These terms and conditions supersede all previous representations, understandings, or agreements and shall prevail notwithstanding any variance with any other terms of any order submitted.
  * You agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions while you are conducting any business on copperbridgemedia.com
  * Any attempt by a user to deliberately damage the website or undermine the legitimate operation of the website is in violation of criminal and civil laws and should such an attempt be made, company reserves the right to seek damages/injunction from any such user to the fullest extent permitted by law.
  * The user agrees to provide authentic and true information. copperbridgemedia.com reserves the right to confirm and validate the information and other details provided by the user at any point of time. If upon confirmation such user details are found not to be true (wholly or partly), copperbridgemedia.com has the right in its sole discretion to reject the registration and debar the user from using the services available on the website, and / or other affiliated websites without prior intimation whatsoever.
  * This user agreement shall be construed in accordance with the law of the land. The Courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction in any proceedings arising out of this agreement.
  * copperbridgemedia.com expressly reserve all intellectual property rights in all text, programs, product(s), processes, technology, content and other materials, which appear on this website. Access to this website does not confer and shall not be considered as conferring upon anyone any license under any of copperbridgemedia.com or any third party’s intellectual property rights.
  * All rights, including copyright, in this website are owned by or licensed to copperbridgemedia.com. Any use of this website or its content, including copying or storing it in whole or part, other than for your own personal, non-commercial use is prohibited without the permission of copperbridgemedia.com. You may not modify, distribute or re-post anything on this website for any purpose.
  * The copperbridgemedia.com names and logos and all the related product(s) and service names, design marks and slogans are the trademarks or service marks of CopperBridge Media. All other marks are the property of their respective companies. No trademark or service mark license is granted in connection with the materials contained on this website. Access to this website does not authorize anyone to use any name, logo or mark in any manner.
  * You understand that by using this website or any services provided by the website, you may encounter content that may be deemed by some to be offensive, indecent, or objectionable, which content may or may not be identified as such.
  * You agree to use the website and any service at your sole risk and that to the fullest extent permitted under applicable law, copperbridgemedia.com shall have no liability to you for content that may be deemed offensive, indecent, or objectionable to you.
  * The users have read and agreed to the copperbridgemedia.com terms and conditions and they have also agreed to receive promotional e-mailers and SMSes.
